What did you read about this?
これ何て読んでしたっけ?
It's J-Pai, J-Pai.
ジーパイです、ジーパイ
Are you trying to get Uncle to come out?
おじさんを出させようとしてるんですか?
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Yeah, let it out.
うん、出して
nice to meet you.
初めまして
That's nice.
いいですね
Aren't you nervous?
緊張してないですか?
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
I feel more nervous though.
僕の方が緊張する感じなんですけど
You have a firm chest, don't you?
胸がしっかりあるじゃないですか?
How many cups is it?
何カップくらいですか?
There are 10 cups.
10カップあります
Is it Zui?
ズイですか?
This is Zui.
ズ イです
It's J-Pai, J-Pai.
ジーパイですね、ジーパイ
That's nice.
いいですね
Have all kinds of men written about Gypai?
ジーパイはいろんな男の人が本をしてきたんですか?
Fair enough.
まあまあ
It's looking good.
いい感じになってますね
Is this a skirt?
これスカートなんですか?
no.
いや
Ah, that's what it is after all.
あ、やっぱそれ系ですよね
It's the one that turns a man into a woman.
男の女の人にしてくれるやつですね
Too bad.
残念って
That's unfortunate.
残念ってね
But even if you catch a glimpse, it's up to you to decide whether it's pants, pants, or pants.
でもチラッと見えても、パンツかミスかパンかってのはこっちが決
What's the point?
め ることなんで
I feel lucky if I see it, but it doesn't change that.
見えたらラッキーと思うのに変わりないっていう
I often get asked this question by everyone.
よく皆さんに質問させてもらってるんですけど
yes.
はい
How long ago was your first experience?
初体験はいくつくらいですか?
It's the spring of my second year of high school.
高2の春です
17 years old.
17歳
The other person was actually her boyfriend at the time.
相手はちゃんと当時の彼氏だったとか、
Or maybe he's not a boyfriend at all.
もしくは全然彼氏でないのに、みたいな
This is someone I like.
好 きな人です
Before we started dating?
まだ付き合う前?
yes.
はい
Were you able to date after that?
その後付き合えたんですか?
home.
いえ
Yes, it's surprisingly common, if you ask me.
そう、意外と多いですよね、これ聞いてると
Isn't that something you can't talk about?
語れとんじゃないんですか、それは?
No, no, I was happy.
いや いや、幸せでした
It happened before that.
その前になったのね
Yes, not at all.
はい、全然
By the way, what are your thoughts after finishing it for the first time?
ちなみに初めて終わった後の感想というか、
Do you have any recollection of it?
覚えてる記憶あります?
Awkward.
気まずい
Doesn't that mean you're happy now?
今幸せだったってことじゃないですか?
Even though you felt happy, did you feel awkward?
幸せな気持ちもありながら、気まずくなっちゃったんですか?
No, I'd say it's awkward.
いや、気まずいっていうか
Is it embarrassing?
気恥ずかしい的な?
What would you say?
なんて言うんだろう
I thought he was a criminal.
犯人してるんだろうって思った
It's like I've come back to the end, or rather I've taken an intolerant side.
何か終わりに帰ったというか、不寛的な味方をしたというか
yes.
はい
It doesn't end with that person,
その人とは、それだけで終わったとかじゃないから、
I said I was happy.
幸せだったって言ったけど
yes.
はい
When the first experience is over, it's awkward.
最初の体験が終わった時は、気まずい
Was it physically painful or not?
体的には痛かったとか、それじゃなかったんですか?
There wasn't.
なかったです
I wonder if it was possible to do it so normally.
そんなに普通にできたっていうか、
I feel like a lot of people are saying that it was painful because it seemed like it was over.
終わらしきりで痛かったっていう人もたくさん言ってる感じなん
in.
で
I met that person just once,
その 人とは、それっきりだけで一回出て、
Or how many times?
それとも何回か
How many times?
何回か
Some times, some times not.
何回か、何回もありなかった
It's frustrating.
悔しいですね
Don't dig into that.
そこを掘り下げるなと
I've reached a good place.
いいところまで行きましたよ
For such a cute girl, I would say no.
こんな可愛い子で、断るというか、
That's amazing.
すごいですね
It's frustrating.
悔しいですね
Do I have to make that Jeep move?
そのジーパイを動きにしないといけないんですか?
regrettable.
悔しい
At that time, I wasn't a Jeepy yet.
その頃まだジーパイじゃなかったんだよ
After a while, there are many people who grow up to the age of high school students.
もうちょっとしたら、高等生ぐらいまで大きくなる人って多い
Isn't it?
じゃない ですか
When did it get so big?
いつぐらいからそんなに大きくなったんですか?
It was always bigger, but I was in JoJo, so
ずっと大きかったんですけど、ジョジョにいたんで、
I was still in that second year of high school.
その高2の時はまだ
Is it about D pie?
Dパイぐらいですか?
It's about E pie compared to F.
FよりのEパイくらいですね
Isn't that enough?
十分じゃないですか
But since then, I've gone up two cups.
でも、その頃からツーカップ上がってるんで
That's amazing.
すごいですね
When I think about it, it still wasn't enough.
って考えると、まだ足りなかったですね
Does that mean you didn't get it a little bit because of that?
そのせいでちょっと届かなかったってことですか?
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
It's not just my boobs, it's my miracle.
おっぱいだけでないよ、私のミラクルと
From then on, I think a lot of things happened to him.
そこからは、彼これいろいろあったと思うんですけど、
Even if you look at this from the outside, it seems abnormal or perverted.
これはちょっと周りから見ても、アブノーマルとか変態チックだ
It was a play that said,
った なとかいうプレイであったり、
It could be a location or something.
場所であったりとかあります
No, there is no such thing.
いや、そういうのないんですよね、
Really.
本当に
I mean, it's relatively normal.
だって割と普通だというか
Yes, it's normal.
はい、普通です
On the other hand, in a slightly abnormal way,
逆に、ちょっとそういうアブノーマル的に、
I might be a little interested in this.
これなら私ちょっと興味あるかもしれない
What about this?
これなら?
Well, there are a lot of things like this, right?
これならというか、いろいろあるじゃないですか、
For example, multiple, or none at all.
例えば複数とか、もしくは全然
No, there's no such thing as a special holy wall.
いや、ないんですね、そういう特殊聖壁みたいなの
Oh, nothing in particular?
あ、特にないんですか
Maybe not in particular.
特にないかも
Then, abnormal is the best.
じゃあ、アブノーマルが一番
I agree.
そうですね
So I thought it would be best to do it secretly at home.
じゃあ家の中でこっそりやるのが最高と
secretly.
こっそり
Other than that, I don't have to worry about being alone.
その他、一人にいられる心配もないと
I guess you could say it secretly.
こっそりといったらあるね
There's nothing moist about it.
しっとりってやつがない
I'd say calm down.
落ち着いてというか
Sleeping?
寝とり?
Ah, sleeping.
あ、寝とり
That's pretty true, but it hasn't been around yet.
結構あれですね、まだあってまもないんですけど、
It was a bit of a lewd thing, but it turned out to be quite a shopping experience.
ちょっとスケベ加減がかなり買い物になってたんですよ
No, no, I think that's a good expression.
いや いや、いい表現かなって
It's a way of putting together expressions.
表現の組み方というか
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうですね
I was good at it.
僕が得意だったんで
Is there a voice of expression even in bed?
ベッドの上でも表現の声は?
Ah, no, I guess so.
あー、いやー、そうでしょう
Hello.
どうもー
I was standing there, but there was something that made me laugh.
俺 は立ってますが、何かひっくり笑いというのが
I agree.
そうですね
Well then, thank you for your continued support today.
ちょっとじゃあ、今日までよろしくお願いします
This is a law, isn't it?
これは法則じゃないですか、これは
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It gets turned over.
めくられるの
Shall we turn this over carefully?
これしっかりめくりましょうか
This lewd guy is about to do a lot of things to me,
このスケベ加減がきもおじさんにいろいろされそうっていうこの、
It's a feeling, or a mindset.
気持ちというか、心構えというか
Be prepared.
心構え
It seemed like something would follow.
なんか後続きそうでした
Excited and excited.
ワクワクドキドキ腹腹的な
I agree.
そうですね
3 stages.
3段階
That's nice.
いいですね
Hey, can I have you put your hands behind your back like this?
ちょっとね、手を後ろにこうやってやってもらっていい?
A little hair.
ちょっと髪の毛を
What did you read about this?
これ、何て読んでしたっけ?
It's J-Pai, J-Pai.
ジーパイです、ジーパイ
I really like that pronunciation.
なんかその発音がいいですよね
It seems like we are called G-Pai,
僕らってなんかジーパイって言いそうですけど、
The intonation is different.
イントネーションが違いますよね
There's food in China, right?
食べ物あるじゃないですか、中国に
It's called G-Pai.
ジーパイっていう
This is a joke.
これはネタです
Is there such a thing as a food jeep?
食べ物のジーパイっていうのがあるんですか?
G-Pai.
ジーパイ
I don't really get it, but it's cute.
なんかよくわかんないけど、かわいい
That's amazing.
すごいなぁ
What is the food jeep?
食べ物のジーパイは何なんですか?
Fruits and things like that.
果物とかその
I forget, but I think it was some sort of huge fried chicken.
忘れたんですけど、多分なんかでっかい唐揚げとかだった気が
do.
する
I don't know.
わか んない
It's embarrassing when it fades.
ちくらったら恥ずかしい
So this was a huge fried chicken, right?
じゃあこれはでっかい唐揚げだったことですね、
These two.
この2つ
Maybe, I don't know.
多分、わかんない
I feel like that's probably what happened.
多分そんなのだったような気がする
I'll look into it a little later.
ちょっと後で調べときます
At Jeepai.
ジーパイで
But I'm wondering if you could express it or say it again.
でもなんか、表現というか、もう一回言ってもらっていいですか?
G-Pai.
ジーパイ
That's cute.
それがかわいい
So can I touch that jeep?
じゃあそのジーパイを触ってもいいですか?
hey.
ね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
But I'll touch it.
でも触ります
Wow, that's a lot of volume.
うわぁ、すごいボリュームが
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What do you think?
どうですか?
Is this really heavy?
これやっぱ重たいんですか?
There are 2 kilograms.
2キロあります
Do you mean 1 kilo each?
1キロずつってこと?
Yes, I measured it.
はい、測ったんですよ
How do you measure it?
どうやって測るの?
Step on the scale normally, then have someone lift it from the front.
普通に体重計乗って、その後に、前から持ち上げてもらって、
I'll ride it.
乗るんですよ
If you do that, you'll be drawn to it by the amount you look like.
そうすると、おっぽい分だけ引かれるんですよ
If you ask me, it's kind of obvious,
言われてみればなんとなくですけど、
Does it press on top of the measurement?
測りの上にドーンって押されるんですか?
No, no, it won't be measured that way.
いやいや、それじゃ計測されないんですよ
That's right.
そうなんだよ
Does that mean I'm 2kg heavier because of this?
このせいで体重が2キロ重くなっちゃってるってこと?
Yes, that's why I always subtract 2 kg and think about it.
はい、だからいつも2キロ引いて考えてます
Oh, wonderful.
ああ、素晴らしい
That's true.
それはそうですよね
That's an old story.
昔の話ですね
Great feet.
素晴らしい足とい
It's the best.
最高ですね
Wait, so you mean knit clothes?
ちょっと じゃあ、ニットの服っていうんですかね
Can I have a ride?
乗りでもらってもいいですか?
already?
もう?
yes.
はい
Please show me the zoo pie.
ズーパイを見せてください
A little zoo pie.
少しズーパイ
yes.
はい
Take it off?
脱ぐ?
yes.
はい
Please take it off.
脱いでください
I think uncles all over the country want to see it.
全国のおじさんが見たがってると思うんで
Zupai?
ズーパイ?
yes.
はい
That's what I want to see most.
僕が一番見たいんですけど
What was that?
何でしたっけ?
Please try again.
もう一回やってください
Zupai.
ズーパイ
That's a good way to say it.
言い方がいい
What do you think, uncle?
どうですか、おじさんに?
I was touched in many ways.
いろいろ触られて
difficult.
難しい
tree
き
I did it.
ました よ
Is this just my imagination?
気のせいですか、これを?
It's just my imagination.
気のせい
That's nice.
いいですね
What do you think, Beachco, can you touch me?
どうですか、ビーチコ触られるの?
tickles.
くすぐったい
That's a wonderful pie.
素晴らしいおズパイですね
Oh, is that a bit like that?
あれ、ちょっとあれですか
Is this revenge because you touched me?
触られたんで仕返しですか?
No, no.
いやいや
My uncle's.
おじさんのが
Are you curious?
気になるんですか?
A little silly.
少しばかし
How does it feel when you touch it, feeling a little silly?
少しばかし気になって、触っている感じはどうですか?
In terms of my current feeling.
今の感触的には
It's a bit bulky.
ちょっともっこい
Is that a good thing?
それ、いいことなんですか?
yes.
はい
I'm trying to confirm.
確認しようとしてます
I'll say it like this.
こう言いますね
Do you want to see it?
見たいですか?
A little silly.
少しばかし
Can I have you pull down your pants for a moment?
ちょっとこれでズボンをずらしてもらっていいですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
I'm standing.
立ってる
What's standing there?
何が立ってるんですか?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
What do you think?
どうですか?
How does it feel in terms of size?
サイズ的に触った感じは?
Look closely.
しっかり目
I was told that my eyes were bare.
しっかり目なんて、はで目って言われました
What an amazing expression.
すごい表現が
What else do you do?
さらにどうするんですか?
moreover?
さらに?
What do you want?
どうしてほしいですか?
I'm fine with doing whatever you want.
もうしたいようにしてくれていいんで
It's given to me.
譲られてくるんだ
Now, excuse me.
では、失礼します
Look closely.
しっかり目
It's out.
出てきましたよ
That's a good look.
しっかり目ですね
What do you think?
どうですか?
What do you want to do with Chin Chin?
チンチンはどうしたいんですか?
What do you want to do?
どうしたい?
It's difficult.
難しいよ
but.
でも
but?
でも?
I want you to include it.
入れてほしい
That's a lie.
っていうような嘘ですね
Just get ahead, just get ahead.
先行っちゃうだけ、先行っちゃうだけ
A classic lie.
定番の嘘
That's not true.
そんなことない
Well then, I believe you.
じゃあ、信じますね
Isn't this cute?
これ可愛くないですか?
Orisame.
おりさめ
What do you think?
どうですか?
Orisame sticky.
おりさめもちもち
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's shaking.
揺れてますよ
Can I have you try it again?
もう一回やってもらっていいですか?
A lot.
ちいっぱい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Are you trying to get the uncle to come out too?
おじさんも出させようとしてるんですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
All the uncles looked at the older sister's blowjob,
みんなおじさんが、お姉さんのフェラーを見て、
I'm chewing.
シコシコしてますよ
What do you think?
どう思いますか?
I want you to look at me and give me a lot.
私を見ていっぱい出してほしい
Please take a look at my full potential.
私のちいっぱいを見て出してください
That's my wish.
本望ですね
Now, say it to the camera.
じゃあ、カメラに向かって言ってください
I asked him to look at my dick and release a lot of cum.
私のちいっぱい見ていっぱい精子出してくださいって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですね
Yes, head this way.
はい、こっちに向かって
please.
どうぞ
What is it?
なんだっけ?
my.
私の
Please release a lot of sperm while looking at my pussy.
私のちいっぱい見ながら精子いっぱい出してください
I'll put it out.
出すよ
This kind of thing is embarrassing.
こういうの恥ずかしい
But he seems happy.
でも、嬉しそうです
Just say one sentence and let it out.
一文言って出して
delicious.
おいしい
It's pretend, right?
ふりでしょ?
It feels good and it hurts.
気持ちいいのと苦しいのとか
Both.
どっちも
Is it mixed?
混ざってる?
I guess you could say it's mixed.
混ざってるっていうか、
I washed it.
洗 ってきたり
Go in and sleep.
入って寝て
Can you go?
いけるかい?
Do you think you can go?
いけると思いますか?
You can go, right?
いけるでしょ?
It ended at age.
歳で終わって
As expected, I guess I'm a little tired.
さすがにね、ちょっとね、疲れてるのかな?
It feels like you can just take a shower and wear it again, right?
シャワー浴びて、もう一回履いていいんやろって感じでしょ?
After all
やっぱ
I'm scared though.
り 怖いんですけど
That's a bit aggressive.
ちょっと積極的ですね
Haven't you touched it?
触ってないですか?
That's nice.
いいですね
Can you squeeze it in?
じいぱいに挟めるんですか?
Do you want to pinch it?
挟みたい?
Can you go?
いけるんですか?
I can go.
いけるよ
Can you go a little longer?
もうちょっといける?
This is how I do it.
こうやってやる
Does everyone really want to pinch it?
みんなやっぱり挟みたがるんですか?
Jipai?
じいぱい?
At the earliest.
じいぱいに
Oh, because it's Jipai.
あ、じいぱいだから
that's why.
だから
It feels so good though.
すっごい気持ちいいんだけど
There will be people like that.
そんな人いっちゃうよ
Are you listening?
聞いてます?
I'm trying to keep it alive.
生かそうとしてるね
Is it okay?
いいの?
No?
ダメ?
That kind of person is no good.
そんな人ダメだよ
You're trying to keep it alive, right?
生かそうとしてるでしょ
You want me to come in while saying that, right?
そう言いながら入れてほしいんでしょ?
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
Can I have you come upstairs?
上に来てもらっていいですか?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいいんですか?
Where in the back?
どこの奥?
Should I put it on?
おつけたほうがいい?
Do I have to wear it?
つけなくていい?
A dog.
ワンコ
Chikubi.
チクビ
What is Naripai?
なりぱいって?
Jiipai.
じいぱい
Get on your knees.
膝を立ててね
My feet here.
僕のここの足
Can I have your hand?
手を持ってもらっていい?
That's all I hear.
それしか聞かないじゃん
What else do you listen to?
それ以外何を聞く?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can you move with this?
これで動ける?
we are moving
僕らが動いてる
Don't give me any information.
ちょっと情報話しないで
Feels good.
気持ちいい
where?
どこ?
we.
僕ら
Feels good.
気持ちいい
where?
どこ?
A dog.
ワンコ
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Yeah, let it out.
うん、出して
Can you do guru?
ギュルってできる?